Guide to the Institute of Pacific Relations Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Part II. American Institute of Pacific Relations, 1926-1959 and Miscellaneous Committee Files
  - American Institute of Pacific Relations, Miscellaneous
    - Testimonials - I.P.R. Integrity (Box 102)
    - Thorp, Willard L. to Ray Lyman Wilbur (Box 102)
    - Vandenbosch, Amry to Ray Lyman Wilbur (Box 102)
    - Welles, Sumner (Box 102)
    - Wilbur, Ray Lyman--Miscellaneous letters to (Box 102)
    - Wright, Quincy (Box 102)
    - American IPR Testimonials (Box 103)
    - Case, Everett--Telegram to Garard Swope (Box 103)
    - Criteria for the Organization of New IPR Groups (Box 103)
    - Decker, C.R. to Gerard Swope (Box 103)
    - deKiewiet, C.W. to Gerard Swope (Box 103)
    - I.P.R. Testimonials (8 Folders) (Box 103)
    - I.P.R. Miscellaneous (Box 103)
    - Letter from Officers of Hawaii IPR (Box 103)
    - Mont Tremblant Conference--Comments (Box 103)
    - Rockefeller Foundation
      - Testimonials (3 Folders) (Box 103)
      - Testimonials --Form Letters (Box 103)
    - Annual Report, 1944-1946, 1948-1950
      (Transferred to Annual Reports, Boxes 273-274)
    - By-Laws of the American Council, IPR (Box 104)
    - Certificate of Incorporation (Box 104)
    - Consent to Change in Name (Box 104)
    - Hatcher, Harlan to W.L.. Holland (Box 104)
    - IPR Bulletin, 1946-1949
    - Malott, Deane W to W.L. Holland (Box 104)
    - Purposes of the Research Advisory Committee of the American Council (Box 104)
    - Resolution on Sale of Stock (Box 104)
    - U.S. Navy Award, 1945 November (Box 104)
  - American Institute of Pacific Relations, 1926-1959 and Miscellaneous Committee Files
    The American Institute of Pacific Relations records are arranged chronologically, and then A-Z by subject. The Miscellaneous Committee records follow these records, and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - 1926-1933
      - Alsberg, Carl L. (6 Folders) (Box 105)
      - Atherton, Frank C. (6 Folders) (Box 105)
      - Australian Council, IPR
        - Miscellaneous (Box 105)
        - Eggleston, F.W. (Box 105)
        - Mills, R.C. (Box 105)
        - Mitchell, Janet (Box 105)
        - Wood, G.L. (Box 105)
      - Baker, Newton (2 Folders) (Box 106)
      - Boyden, Roland W. (Box 106)
      - Buesst, Tristan (Box 106)
      - Carnegie Corporation--Keppel, F.P. (Box 106)
      - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray (Box 106)
        - Haskell, Henry (Box 106)
        - Pritchett, Henry (Box 106)
        - Washington Office (Box 106)
      - Carter, Edward C. (Box 106)
      - Canadian Institute of International Affairs (Box 106)
      - Chamberlain, Joseph P.
        - General (Box 107)
        - Immigration (Box 107)
      - Cheng, Ronald Y.S. (Box 107)
      - Chicago Office
        - Bell, Helen (Box 107)
        - Welling, Harriet (Box 107)
        - World's Fair, 1933 (Box 107)
      - China, IPR
        - General (Box 107)
        - Chen, L.T. (4 Folders) (Box 107)
        - Hu Shih (Box 107)
        - Liang, H.S. (Box 107)
        - Lieh, D.K. (Box 107)
        - Liu Yu-wan (2 Folders) (Box 107)
        - Minutes (Box 107)
        - Ting, Y.K. (Box 107)
        - Yui, David (2 Folders) (Box 107)
      - Comstock, Ada L. (Box 108)
      - Condliffe, John B. (Box 108)
      - Curtis, Mr, and Mrs. Lionel (3 Folders) (Box 108)
      - Datta, S.K. (Box 109)
      - Davis, J. Merle (8 Folders) (Box 109)
      - Eggleston, Fred W. (Box 110)
      - Foreign Trade Council (Box 110)
      - Form Letters (10 Folders) (Box 110)
      - French Group, IPR
        - General (Box 110)
        - Lévy, Roger (Box 110)
      - Eggleston, Fred W. (Box 110)
      - Greene, Jerome D.
        - (11 Folders) (Box 111)
        - (8 Folders) (Box 112)
      - Gunn, Selskar (Box 112)
      - Hawaiian Group, I.P.R. (Box 113)
      - Hinder, Eleanor (Box 113)
      - Honolulu IPR
        - General (Box 113)
        - Education (Box 113)
        - International Research Committee (Box 113)
        - James, Neill (Box 113)
        - Research (Box 113)
      - Hornbeck, Stanley K. (Box 113)
      - Howland, Charles P. (Box 113)
      - Kilpatrick, William H. (Box 113)
      - Korean Group, IPR (Box 113)
      - Loomis, Charles F.
        - (10 Folders) (Box 114)
        - Travel Letters (Box 114)
      - Lytton Report (Box 114)
      - Me (Box 115)
      - McClatchy, V.S. (Box 115)
      - Mei Lan-fang (Box 115)
      - Pan-American Congress (Box 115)
      - Pan-Pacific Union (Box 115)
      - Price, Maurice (Box 115)
      - Philippine Council, IPR (Box 115)
      - Royal Institute of International Affairs
        - Reports (Box 115)
        - Macadam, Ivison (Box 115)
      - San Francisco Office Organization (Box 115)
      - Shotwell, James T. (10 Folders) (Box 116)
      - Strong, Edward K. (Box 116)
      - Sze, Alfred Sao-Ke (Box 116)
      - Treasury Department--Bureau of Customs (Box 117)
      - Wilbur, Ray Lyman (4 Folders) (Box 117)
      - William, Maurice
        - General (Box 117)
        - Correspondence (Box 117)
        - Manuscript (Box 117)
      - Wittfogel, Karl August
        - Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced German Scholars (Box 117)
        - Pamphlets (Box 117)
        - Personal (2 Folders) (Box 117)
        - Volume on China (Box 117)
      - Woolley, Mary E. (Box 118)
      - Wright, Philip G. (Box 118)
      - Wright, Quincy (Box 118)
      - Yen, Hawkling (Box 118)
      - Young, Owen D (Box 118)
    - 1933-1938
      - Newspapers Clippings on Various Topics, 1938 (Box 160)
        - American-Philippine Relations (Box 160)
        - Austria (Box 160)
        - European Politics (Box 160)
        - John Gunther's Dispatches (Box 160)
        - John Gunther's Interview with Chiang Kai-shek (Box 160)
        - Book Reviews (Box 160)
        - Canadian Transport and Mining Developments (Box 160)
        - Chinese Aviation (Box 160)
        - Chinese Political Unification and Military Progress (Box 160)
        - Dostoevsky and Revolution (Box 160)
        - Magnitogorsk (Box 160)
        - Nanking Puppet Regime (Box 160)
        - Nazi Army Scandal (Box 160)
        - Neutralization of Philippines (Box 160)
        - State Control of Industry in Japan (Box 160)
        - USA
          - Sharecroppers (Box 160)
          - Spanish Policy (Box 160)
        - USSR--General (Box 160)
        - What America is Reading (Box 160)
      - A (Box 119)
      - Academy of Political Science (Box 119)
      - Ackerman, Carl W. (Box 119)
      - Alexander, Wallace M (Box 119)
      - Allen, Esther R (Box 119)
      - Allen, George & Unwin Ltd. (Box 119)
      - Alsberg, Carl L (Box 119)
      - Amerasia (Box 119)
      - American Acadeny of Political and Social Science (Box 119)
      - American Asiatic Association
        - Chevalier, John B. (Box 119)
        - Cole, Howard E. (Box 119)
      - American Association for Adult Education--Cartwright, Morse A. (Box 119)
      - American Council of Learned Societies
        - General (Box 119)
        - Graves, Mortimer (Box 119)
        - Joint Committee on Materials for Research (Box 119)
      - American Economic Mission to China (Box 119)
      - American Friends Service Committee (Box 119)
      - American Geographical Society (Box 119)
      - American Organizations (Box 120)
      - American Council, IPR--Executive Committee Meeting, 1938 September 20 (Box 120)
      - Anderson, Elam J. (Box 120)
      - Andrews, Benjamin R (Box 120)
      - Annual Reports (Box 120)
      - Arnold, Julean (Box 120)
      - Atherton, Franl C (Box 120)
      - Australian Council, IPR
        - General (Box 120)
        - Heydon, P.R. (Box 120)
        - Hinder, Eleanor (Box 120)
      - Auxiliary Publication Service (Box 120)
      - Ba (Box 120)
      - Babcock, Earle B (Box 120)
      - Bain, H. Foster (Box 120)
      - Baker, Newton D. (Box 120)
      - Baker, O.E. (Box 120)
      - Balch, A,C. (Box 120)
      - Barber, Joseph (Box 120)
      - Barnum, Cyrus P. (Box 120)
      - Basic English--Tyler, Charlotte (Box 120)
      - Bates, M. Searle (Box 120)
      - Belshaw, Horace (Box 121)
      - Bi (Box 121)
      - Bibliography Project (Box 121)
      - Biggerstaff, Knight (Box 121)
      - Binder, Carroll (Box 121)
      - Blakeslee, George H. (Box 121)
      - Bloch, Kurt (Box 121)
      - The Booklist (Box 121)
      - Br-Bu (Box 121)
      - Bradley, Phillips (Box 121)
      - Branting, Sonja (Box 121)
      - Bratter, Herbert M. (Box 121)
      - British Who's Who (Box 121)
      - Brockman, Fletcher S. (Box 121)
      - Buchanan, D.H. (Box 121)
      - Buck, J. Lossing (Box 121)
      - Buck, Pearl S. (Box 121)
      - Burden, William A.M. (Box 121)
      - Bureau of University Travel (Box 121)
      - C (Box 122)
      - California Council on Oriental Relations (Box 122)
      - California Joint Immigration Committee (Box 122)
      - Canada Looks East--Strange, William (Box 122)
      - Canadian Institute of International Affairs
        - General (Box 122)
        - Dafoe, J.W. (Box 122)
        - Reid, Prescott (Box 122)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 122)
      - Cannon, Marian (Box 122)
      - Carnegie Corporation
        - General (Box 122)
        - Appeal, 1993 (Box 122)
        - Keppel, Frederick P. (Box 122)
      - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace
        - General (Box 122)
        - Butler, Nicholas Murray (Box 122)
        - Haskell, Henry (Box 122)
        - Pritchett, Henry S. (Box 122)
        - Washington Office (Box 122)
      - Carter, Edward C. (Box 123)
      - Carter, Edward C. - Boston Visit (Box 123)
      - Case, Everett (Box 123)
      - Catt, Carrie Chapman (Box 123)
      - Cause and Cure of War (Box 123)
      - Ch (Box 123)
      - Chaddock, Helen (Box 123)
      - Chamberlain, Joseph (Box 123)
      - Chandler, Harry (Box 123)
      - Chang, P.C. (Box 123)
      - Chapman, Royal N. (Box 123)
      - Chatterjee, M.N. (Box 123)
      - Cherrington, Ben (Box 123)
      - Chi, Ch’ao-ting (Box 123)
      - Chicago IPR
        - General (Box 123)
        - Houghteling, James L. (Box 123)
        - Shillinglaw, Daniel L. (Box 123)
      - Chicago (University) Press
        - General (Box 123)
        - Bean, Donald (Box 123)
        - Tyler, Marjorie (Box 123)
      - China Institute in America--Meng, Chih (Box 123)
      - China IPR
        - General (Box 123)
        - Hu Shih (Box 123)
        - Liu Yu-van (Box 123)
      - Chinese Consulate General (Box 123)
      - Chinese Legation (Box 123)
      - Christy, Arthur E. (Box 123)
      - Clyde, Paul H. (Box 124)
      - Co (Box 124)
      - Coleman, Norman F. (Box 124)
      - Collins, Alan C. (Box 124)
      - Coltman, Robert (Box 124)
      - Comstock, Ada L. (Box 124)
      - Condliffe, John B. (Box 124)
      - Contributors' Information Service (Box 124)
      - Coolidge, Harold J. (Box 124)
      - Council on Foreign Relations
        - General (Box 124)
        - Dean, Edgar P. (Box 124)
        - Mallory, Walter H. (Box 124)
      - Counts, George S. (Box 124)
      - Cowdrey, Jane (Box 124)
      - Cowper, Norman (Box 124)
      - Cressey, George B. (Box 124)
      - Crocker, Stuart M. (Box 124)
      - Cromwell, Doris Duke (Box 124)
      - Crow, Allen B. (Box 124)
      - Current History Advisory Board (Box 124)
      - D (Box 125)
      - Datta, S.K. (Box 125)
      - Davis, Norman H. (Box 125)
      - Day, John Company (Box 125)
      - Dennett, Tyler (Box 125)
      - Dennison, Eleanor (Box 125)
      - Detzer, Dorothy (Box 125)
      - Do-Dy (Box 125)
      - Doubleday, Doran and Company (Box 125)
      - DuBois, Rachel Davis (Box 125)
      - Duggan, Lawrence (Box 125)
      - Dunham, Donald C. (Box 125)
      - Dunlap, Jack W. (Box 125)
      - E (Box 125)
      - Earnshaw, Ruth (Box 125)
      - Elliston, H.B. (Box 125)
      - Elmhirst Committee (Box 125)
      - Epstein, Fritz (Box 125)
      - Erdman, H.E. (Box 125)
      - Esberg, Alfred I. (Box 125)
      - Fa-Fi (Box 126)
      - Fahs, Charles Burton (Box 126)
      - Falk Foundation (Box 126)
      - Farley, Miriam S. (Box 126)
      - Feakins, William B. (Box 126)
      - Feetham, Richard (Box 126)
      - Field, Frederick V.
        - General (Box 126)
        - Office (Box 126)
      - Films--Binkley Project (Box 126)
      - Fischer, Louis (Box 126)
      - Fisher, Galen M.
        - General (Box 126)
        - Private Correspondence (Box 126)
      - Fisher, H.H. (Box 126)
      - Fisher, Sterling (Box 126)
      - Fl (Box 126)
      - Foreign Policy Association (Box 127)
        - Buell, Raymond (Box 127)
        - Ogden, Esther (Box 127)
      - Form File
        - 1937 (two Folders) (Box 127)
        - 1938 (two Folders) (Box 127)
      - Fosdick, Raymond B. (Box 127)
      - Freeman, Miller (Box 127)
      - French IPR (Box 127)
      - Friedman, Irving S. (Box 127)
      - Fuchs, Walter (Box 127)
      - Ga-Ge (Box 128)
      - General Motors Export Company--Mooney, James D. (Box 128)
      - Gl-Gu (Box 128)
      - Goodrich, L. Carrington (Box 128)
      - Greene, Jerome D. (Box 128)
      - Greene, Roger S. (Box 128)
      - Greenwood, George H. (Box 128)
      - Griswold, A. Whitney (Box 128)
      - Ha (Box 128)
      - Hall, Russell E. (Box 128)
      - Handy, Edward S.C. (Box 128)
      - Hanwell, Norman D. (Box 128)
      - Haring, Douglas G. (Box 128)
      - Harper, Heber (Box 128)
      - Harris, Paul (Box 128)
      - Hart, Nancy (Box 128)
      - Hauser, Ernest O. (Box 128)
      - Hawaii Group, IPR (Box 128)
      - He-Hi (Box 129)
      - Ho-Hu (Box 129)
      - Hobbs, Jean (Box 129)
      - Holcombe, Arthur N. (Box 129)
      - Holden, Ashley E. (Box 129)
      - Holland, W.L. (Box 129)
      - Honolulu, IPR
        - General (Box 129)
        - Budd, Idell (Box 129)
        - Hawaiian Incursion in Advisory Committee (Box 129)
        - James, Neill (Box 129)
        - Simpich, Frederick (Box 129)
      - Hotels (Box 129)
      - Hoyt, Nancy (Box 129)
      - Hughes, Nancy S. (Box 129)
      - Hume, Edward H. (Box 129)
      - Hunter, Edith (Box 129)
      - I (Box 129)
      - Immigration (Box 129)
      - India (Box 130)
      - Institute for Social and Economic Research (Box 130)
      - Institute of International Education
        - Duggan. (Box 130)
        - Institute Name (Box 130)
      - Institute of Oriental Studies (Box 130)
      - Institute of Pacific Relations--Notes (Box 130)
      - Institute of Public Affairs-University of Virginia (Box 130)
      - Institute of Social Research (Box 130)
      - International Geographical Congress (Box 130)
      - International Missionary Council (Box 130)
      - International Societies and Organizations--Miscellaneous (Box 130)
      - Interorganizational Cooperation (Box 130)
      - Jäckh, Ernst (Box 131)
      - Jameson, R.D. (Box 131)
      - Jessup, Philip C. (Box 131)
      - Johnson, Nelson T. (Box 131)
      - Ka-Ke (Box 131)
      - Kantorovich, Anatole--Manuscript (Box 131)
      - Kennard, J. Spencer (Box 131)
      - Ki-Kr (Box 131)
      - Klineberg, Otto (Box 131)
      - La-Le (Box 131)
      - Lattimore, Owen, 1936-1939 (Box 131)
      - Le (Box 132)
      - League of Women Voters (Box 132)
      - Lear, Harry B (Box 132)
      - Leavens, Dickson H. (Box 132)
      - Lederer, Emil (Box 132)
      - Leith, C.K. (Box 132)
      - Li-Ly (Box 132)
      - Li, K.C. (Box 132)
      - Li, Richard S.M. (Box 132)
      - Library of Congress (Box 132)
      - Library of International Relations, 1933-1937 (Box 132)
      - Lin, Mousheng (Box 132)
      - Little, Herbert (Box 132)
      - Living Age (Box 132)
      - Lockwood, W.W. (Box 133)
      - Loomis, Charles F.
        - 1934-1937 (Box 133)
        - Los Angeles (Box 133)
      - Lorwin, Lewis L. (Box 133)
      - Los Angeles Chamber of Commerce (Box 133)
      - Luce, Henry R. (Box 133)
      - Lytton, Lord (Box 133)
      - M (Box 134)
      - Mc (Box 134)
      - McCoy, Frank (Box 134)
      - McCulloch, Rhoda E. (Box 134)
      - McGraw, Don (Box 134)
      - MacIver, Robert M. (Box 134)
      - Macmillan Company (Box 134)
      - MacMurray, John V.A. (Box 134)
      - Manchuria--Fugitive Material (Box 134)
      - Maps
        - General (Box 134)
        - Racks (Box 134)
        - Visual Education (Box 134)
      - Martin, Charles E. (Box 134)
      - May Visit (Box 134)
      - Me (Box 134)
      - Mexican Participation (Box 134)
      - Middleton, Keith J. (Box 135)
      - Midkiff, Frank E. (Box 135)
      - Milbank Memorial Fund (Box 135)
      - Miller, Ellaroya (Box 135)
      - Miller, Spencer (Box 135)
      - Millikan, Robert A. (Box 135)
      - Mineral Inquiry (Box 135)
      - Mitchell, Kate L. (Box 135)
      - Mitrany, David (Box 135)
      - Mo-Mu (Box 135)
      - Moore, Harriet L. (Box 135)
      - Moore, Walden (Box 135)
      - Morrisson, Mary (Box 135)
      - Morrisson, William D.F. (Box 135)
      - Moscow Trials (Box 135)
      - Moulton, Harold G. (Box 135)
      - Munro, William B. (Box 135)
      - Murrow, Edward R. (Box 135)
      - N (Box 136)
      - National Advisory Council on Radio in Education - Tyson, Levering (Box 136)
      - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 136)
      - National Council for Prevention of War (Box 136)
      - National Council of Education (Box 136)
      - National Foreign Trade Council (Box 136)
      - National Institute of Immigrant Welfare (Box 136)
      - National Organizations and Societies--Miscellaneous (Box 136)
      - National Peace Conference (Box 136)
      - National Unemployed League (Box 136)
      - Netherlands and Netherlands-Indies (Box 137)
        - General (Box 137)
        - Boeke, J.H. (Box 137)
        - Economic Handbook (Box 137)
        - Kollewijn, R.D. (Box 137)
        - Moll, J. Th. (Box 137)
        - van Kan, J. (Box 137)
      - New Commonwealth (Box 137)
      - New Orient Society (Box 137)
      - New York City Committee for Public Adult Education (Box 137)
      - New Zealand, IPR
        - General (Box 137)
        - McIntosh, A.D. (Box 137)
        - Nash, Walter (Box 137)
        - Scholefield, Guy H. (Box 137)
      - Normano, J.F. (Box 137)
      - Northwest--General (Box 137)
      - Nugent, Donald R. (Box 137)
      - Obana, Tautomu (Box 138)
      - Office Memos (Box 138)
      - Open Road (Box 138)
      - Orchard, John E. (Box 138)
      - Oriental Economist (Box 138)
      - Oxford University Press (Box 138)
      - Pa-Ph (Box 138)
      - Pacific Affairs, 1936-1939 (Box 138)
      - Pacific Council Meeting (Box 138)
      - Pacific Pilot (Box 138)
      - Palmer, Frank--Federated Press (Box 138)
      - Parker, Philo W. (Box 138)
      - Payne Fund
        - Crandall, Ella P. (Box 138)
        - Evans, S. Howard (Box 138)
      - Peake, Cyrus H. (Box 138)
      - Peffer, Nathaniel (Box 138)
      - Pendle Hill (Box 138)
      - Penrose, E.E. (Box 138)
      - Philippine Council, IPR--General (Box 138)
      - Philippine Pensionados
        - Luciano, Augusto (Box 138)
        - Penlilio, Luis (Box 138)
      - Pi (Box 139)
      - Pictorial Statistics (Box 139)
      - Population Association of America (Box 139)
      - Porter, Catherine
        - General (Box 139)
        - Philippine Project (Box 139)
      - Price, Ernest B. (Box 139)
      - Price, Maurice T. (Box 139)
      - Pritchard, E.H. (Box 139)
      - Problems of the Pacific (Box 139)
      - Propaganda Study (Box 139)
      - Public Opinion--Miscellaneous (Box 139)
      - Publications (Box 139)
      - Publishers (Box 139)
      - Purcell, Victor (Box 139)
      - Pyke, Richard (Box 139)
      - Quigley, Harold S. (Box 140)
      - Ra-Re (Box 140)
      - Race Relations (Box 140)
      - Radio (Box 140)
      - Radius, Walter A. (Box 140)
      - Rates (Box 140)
      - Reinhardt, Aurelia (Box 140)
      - Reisner, John H. (Box 140)
      - Remer, C.F. (Box 140)
      - Rhoads, Charles J. (Box 140)
      - Rich, Raymond T. (Box 140)
      - Rivers, William C. (Box 140)
      - Ro (Box 140)
      - Robinson, Geroid (Box 140)
      - Rockefeller
        - Davison Fund (Box 140)
        - Family (Box 140)
        - 1935 Appeal (Box 140)
        - Stevens, David H. (Box 140)
      - Rockefeller Foundation
        - General (Box 140)
        - Day, Edmund E. (Box 140)
        - Gunn, Selskar M (Box 140)
      - Rogers, James H. (Box 141)
      - Roman, Agnes (Box 141)
      - Romm, Vladimir (Box 141)
      - Rosenwald Fund
        - General (Box 141)
        - Embree, Edwin R. (Box 141)
        - Stern, Alfred K. (Box 141)
      - Rosinski, Herbert (two Folders) (Box 141)
      - Rowell, Chester H. (Box 141)
      - Royal Institute of International Affairs
        - General (two Folders) (Box 141)
        - Cleeve, Margaret E. (two Folders) (Box 141)
        - Coke, Gerald (Box 141)
        - Macadam, Ivison S (Box 141)
        - Rose, Archibald (Box 141)
        - Toynbee, Arnold J. (Box 141)
      - Rugg, Harold (Box 141)
      - Russian Language School (Box 141)
      - Russian Studies Conference (Box 141)
      - Sa-Sc (Box 142)
      - Sachs, Alexander (Box 142)
      - Sakabe, Shigeyashi (Box 142)
      - San Francisco 1937-1938
        - General (Box 142)
        - Oakie, John H. (Box 142)
      - Scott, Ernest (Box 142)
      - Se-Sh (Box 142)
      - Shank, Corwin S. (Box 142)
      - Sheffield, Alfred D. (Box 142)
      - Shields, Randolph (Box 142)
      - Shiman, Russell (Box 142)
      - Shimbun Rengo (Box 142)
      - Shotwell, James T.
        - General (Box 142)
        - Soviet Project (Box 142)
      - Simpson, John (Box 143)
      - Skvirsky, Boris (Box 143)
      - Slade, Caroline (Box 143)
      - Sm-Sp (Box 143)
      - Social Science Research Conference of the Pacific Coast (Box 143)
      - Social Science Research Council -
        - General (Box 143)
        - Crane, Robert T. (Box 143)
        - 1937 Inquiry (Box 143)
        - Young, Donald (Box 143)
      - Society for Japanese Studies (Box 143)
      - Sokolsky, George (Box 143)
      - South Manchuria Railway Company (Box 143)
      - Southern California Group (Box 143)
      - Soviet Consulate (Box 143)
      - Soviet, IPR
        - General (Box 143)
        - Memo on Methods of Investigation of Standard of Living (Box 143)
      - Soviet Embassy (Box 143)
      - Soviet Invitation to World Conference (Box 143)
      - Sproul, Robert G. (Box 143)
      - Spykman, Nicholas J. (Box 143)
      - St (Box 143)
      - Steiner, Jesse (Box 143)
      - Stimson, Henry L. (Box 143)
      - Stockton, Philip (Box 143)
      - Stokowska, Evangeline (Box 143)
      - Strong, Sydney (Box 143)
      - Stuart, J. Leighton (Box 143)
      - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays (Box 143)
      - Ta-Ty (Box 144)
      - Taussig, Frank W. (Box 144)
      - Tawney, R.H. (Box 144)
      - Taylor, Margaret (Box 144)
      - Thompson, Caroline Huston (Box 144)
      - Ting, Vung Yuin (Box 144)
      - Tomkinson, Leonard (Box 144)
      - Tozzer, Alfred W. (Box 144)
      - Trewartha, Glenn T. (Box 144)
      - Tupper, Eleanor (Box 144)
      - U (Box 144)
      - United States Departments, Washington
        - General (Box 144)
        - Department of Commerce (Box 144)
        - Department of Interior (Box 144)
        - Department of State (Box 144)
      - Universities (Box 144)
      - Van Kleeck, Mary (Box 145)
      - Veatch, Roy (Box 145)
      - von KleinSmid, Rufus (Box 145)
      - von Waldheim, Harald (Box 145)
      - W (Box 145)
      - Walsh, Richard J. (Box 145)
      - Webb, Alice L. (Box 145)
      - Welling, Harriet (Box 145)
      - Wentworth, Edna (Box 145)
      - Wertheim, Barbara (Box 145)
      - Wertheim, Maurice (Box 145)
      - Weetheimer, Fritz (Box 145)
      - Wh (Box 145)
      - Whyte, Frederick (Box 145)
      - Wickersham, George W. (Box 145)
      - Wilbur, Ray Lyman (Box 145)